Christopher Inzinga

210 Highland Drive, Henniker, NH, 0324;

□ (603) 715-4788 | Schris@inzinga.com | Acinzinga.com | Ocinzinga

Summary _____

I am a current Information Technology student with a passion for cyber security topics. Independently I have pursued multiple professional certifications in the field. From these certifications I have demonstrated a proficiency in network reconnaissance, web exploitation, and privilege escalation among other topics. As a security researcher and bug bounty hunter, I have worked with companies to identify, exploit, and report vulnerabilities I discovered in their web applications.

Work Experience

Red Sky Alliance

 Cyber Threat Intelligence Intern
 December. 2020 - Present

• Conducted open source information gathering to develop actionable intelligence for businesses. Performed analysis and critical thinking to develop successful reports and verbal presentations.

BAE Systems Radford, Virginia

STUDENT INTERN

June. 2017 - July. 2017

New Boston, NH

• Shadowed employees at Radford Army Ammunitions Plant to learn professional Chemical Engineering practices and procedures.

Certifications & Awards

CERTIFICATIONS

CRTP, Pentester Academy Certified Red Team Professional	May. 2020
eWPT, eLearnSecurity Web Application Penetration Tester	December. 2019
OSCP , Offensive Security Certified Professional	September. 2019
Security+, CompTIA Security+	July. 2019
eJPT, eLearnSecurity Junior Penetration Tester	July. 2019
FE Chemical, Fundamentals of Engineering Exam (Chemical Engineering)	February. 2019
CEH, EC-Council Certified Ethical Hacker	August. 2018

AWARDS

Eagle Scout, Boy Scouts of America

June. 2013

Cyber Security Achievements _____

BugCrowd Bug Bounty Hunter, Achieved Global Ranking of Top 100	February. 2021
BugCrowd Bug Bounty Hunter, Q3 MVP	November. 2020
BugCrowd Bug Bounty Hunter, Q2 MVP	August. 2020
Synack Red Team, Passed numerous technical challenges to join the elite SRT (~11% acceptance rate)	June. 2020
CVE-2020-10557, AContent v1.4 Remote Code Execution	March. 2020
Cowrie Honeypot , Self-hosted an intentionally vulnerable server to analyze malware samples in the wild	January. 2020
CVE-2020-7209, Hewlett Packard Enterprise LinuxKI v6.0-1 Remote Code Execution	January. 2020
CVE-2020-6637, OpenSIS v7.3 Unauthenticated SQL Injection	January. 2020
CVE-2019-19908, phpMyChat v1.98 Cross Site Scripting	December. 2019

Education

University of New Hampshire

Manchester, NH

B.S IN COMPUTER INFORMATION SYSTEMS

February 2021 - Present

• Expected to graduate in May 2022

NHTI - Concord's Community College

Concord, NH

A.S IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (NETWORKING)

September 2019 - Present

• Expected to graduate in May 2021

FEBRUARY 15, 2021 CHRIS INZINGA · RÉSUMÉ